RONNY HARTONO

Senior Developer

PROFILE

I have a great background education and have a good management skill. I mastering several programming language such as Delphi, macro, Php, html, javascript and Java, I also mastering sql language such as Sql Server and MySql, I also have a experience in working at organization

SKILLS

Android Studio

Office & Windows

Java & Delphi

PHP ,HTML & JavaScript

MySQL & SQL Server

Crystal Report & Jasperreport

BIODATA

Place and Date of Birth Surabaya, 15-11-1984

Address

Kapasan Kidul 3 / 2 , Surabaya

Email

Ronnyhartono9@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Associate Degree Informatics Management, 2004-2007 – ISTTS

Bachelor Degree Bussiness Information System, 2007-2009 – ISTTS

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. Surya Timur Sakti Jatim , April 2009 – October 2009 IT Staff

Create software from Delphi 7 integrate with ms access to receive data from police department and process that data become report sales of vehicle in Indonesia overall

Create macro from excel to report dealer's performance

PT. Tohitindo Multicraft Industries , July 2010 – December 2010 IT Staff

Create software from PHP and mysql for record transaction everyday

PT. Sadhana, December 2010 – now

IT Staff

Create software to maintain cash and bank transaction every day , and maintain Account payable also Account Receivable

Create android app to record GPS position and send to server via PHP

Create web for maintain employee work and progress with PHP, javascript and mysql

Create software to receive guest and send message directly into android phone with java, android studio and firebase

Create web online store with PHP, javascript and mysql.

Improve web with latest framework like Laravel or CI